I've done something like this before.
こういうのやってたことある
Oh my.
あらー
Ahhh.
あーん
copper?
どう?
What do you think?
どうだろう
Then I'll give you this.
じゃあこれ渡すのね
Beautiful water.
綺麗なお水
What is that called?
それはなんていうんですか?
Clear water.
清水
It's not Shimizu.
清水じゃない
It's salt.
塩です
Aren't you starting to want to include it?
入れたくなってきたんじゃないんですか?
Isn't that your uncle?
それはおじさんの方じゃないの?
Can I ask you to do your best?
頑張ってもらっていいですか?
More and more.
ど んどん
Ah.
あっ
Yes, well.
はい、よく
Are you sure the clothes you just wore are Enogy?
さっきの服をやっぱりエノジーなんですか?
No, I just bought it.
いや ー、めっちゃ買ったばっかなんですよ、
recently.
最近
Hey, look at those clothes.
ね え、あの服ちょっと
So, I attached the handle.
で、取り手貼ったんですけど
I just can't help it.
ちょっと仕方ないってことで
Well, if you do that too much, you won't be able to walk on the water.
まあまあ、あんまりあれと水道は歩けなくなっちゃいますもんね、
If only we were wearing the same clothes.
同じ服やったらね
Do you have any clothes for your baby?
おねさん服ないですか?
that's right.
そうです
It feels like something better than Disney.
ディズニーのマシマシって感じです
What do you think, this first time?
どうですか、この1回目ってなんかこう、
Did something happen on the men's internet?
男ネットで何かありましたか?
It's nothing special and it's fun.
なんもなくて、楽しいです
I mean, it's a male Hideri.
男ヒデリってことですね
Oh, my name is Hideri.
あ、ヒデリが名前が
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
What were you doing?
どうしてたの?
There are lonely nights, right?
寂しい夜もあるじゃないですか
Well, you can imagine that.
まあまあ、それはご想像に
As you can imagine.
ご想像に
That's what it means.
ってことはそういうことですね
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Oh, okay.
あら、まあまあ
What do you think?
どうだろう
Well then, I'll give you this.
じゃあ、これ渡すんで
Try it out.
実 践してみて
difficult.
難しい
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ美しい
It doesn't have to be difficult.
難しくならなくても大丈夫ですよ
yeah?
ん?
anxiety.
心配
Let's all make her into a woman with a mission.
みんなでミッションつけながらの女にしてね
Beautiful, really.
美しい、めっちゃ
Through the screen.
画面越しね
There are also a lot of older fans watching.
またファンのおじさんがいっぱい見てますよ
Please leave a comment.
コメントお願いします
Are you removing it?
抜いてますか?
A little sweet.
ちょっと甘い
That's amazing.
すごいな
Please be more cute.
もっと可愛くいってください
Cute?
可愛く?
Is it getting bigger?
大きくなってますか?
Please pull out as much as I can.
私でいっぱい抜いてくださいね
yeah?
ん?
What do you mean?
って言うの?
Please pull out as much as I can.
私でいっぱい抜いてくださいね
It seems contrived.
わざとらしい
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ美しい
Do you do it on-site?
現場で行ったりするんですか?
do.
する
I also want to see where I'm going.
行 くところも見たいな
Please also show me where you are going.
行くところも見せてください
It might take some time.
時間かかるかも
I'll give you a lot of attention.
めっちゃくりまつかせる
What should I do?
どうすると?
In the center of Kuri-chan.
くりちゃんの中心にとか
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり
I have to move forward quickly.
急に進めないと
feel ill.
気 持ち悪い
My waist is getting higher though.
腰が上がってきてますけど
Is it better to be strong?
強い方がいいですか?
Please try to be better.
こっちよくしてみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I couldn't open it for a long time.
ずっと開かなくて
Are you about to fall?
もう落ちそうですか?
Please let me know when you go properly.
ちゃん と行くとき教えてね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Beautiful water.
綺麗なお水
Clear water.
清水
It's salt.
塩です
If it was Shimizu, it would have been different.
清水だったら違うものになっちゃった
Which one is it?
どっちなんですか?
Salt.
お塩
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
It doesn't reach me.
届かない
where?
どこ?
I can have it.
持てる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Don't look.
見ないで
Please don't look.
見ないでください
Get out of my way.
手を抜けて
Feelings that I'm used to seeing.
見慣れてる感想を
A word to everyone across the country.
全国の皆さんに一言
Please don't watch it because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから見ないでください
Look happy
うれしそうな顔して
Because.
る から
It's hard to see.
見にくいんだよね
This way?
こっち?
Did you ride?
乗った?
Were you seen at all?
しまっか見られてた?
Please show me.
から、見せて
What?
何を?
What should I do?
どうする?
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
There is always one truth.
真実はいつも一つ
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
I thought you liked it.
好きかと思って
I'll be out there.
そこに出ちゃいますよ
Is it okay?
いい んですか?
No.
ダメ
Let's be durable
耐久をしてもらおう
and.
と
It became sweet.
甘 くなった
Isn't the shower long?
シャワー長くない?
That's not true.
そんなことないよ
I thought you were tired.
疲れてるのかと思った
That's not true.
そんなことない
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
amazing?
すごい?
Something amazing?
何かすごい?
My right hand is doing something a bit.
右手がちょっと何かしてますけど
Take the pasta.
パスタを取って
Shall I pinch you while looking at you?
こっち見ながら挟んであげよっか?
With G pie.
Gパイで
Take the G-pie.
Gパイを取って
Since I can't send a signal for that, I'll leave it to you.
それを合図を送れないので、お任せします
Shall I pinch it?
挟んであげようか?
With G pie.
Gパイで
What do you think of this hair?
この髪どう?
It's cute.
可愛いです
Looks like I'll lose first.
先落とそう
Because it's cross-sectional hair.
断面ヘアだから
I'll put it behind you.
後ろにするね
I agree.
そうだね
Because I use G-pie.
Gパイ使うから
Just a little more.
もう ちょっと
copper?
どう?
G-pie.
Gパイ
Say G-pie.
Gパイって言って
G-pie.
Gパイ
Don't mess around like that.
そんな骨くいまわしちゃダメだよ
My head was also buzzing.
頭もサワサワしながら
It's like raising bread.
まるでパンを起こねるかのように
Please sandwich it with G pie.
Gパイで挟んでください
what?
何ですか?
The face of the old man rubbing it.
揉んでるおじさんの顔は
Highest.
最高
Because you seem to like this.
これが好きみたいだから
But you must have wanted to put it in that much, haven't you?
でもそんなに入れたくなってきたんじゃないんですか?
Aren't you starting to want to include it?
入れたくなってきたんじゃないんですか?
Isn't that your uncle?
それはおじさんのほうじゃないの?
It's okay to try your best.
頑張ってもいいです
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
Can I put it in?
入れてもいいの?
G-pie.
Gパイ
Can you please come upstairs?
このまま上に来てくれる?
To the right.
右に
right?
右?
This way?
こっちか
That's right, my face is starting to look out of place.
そうそう、顔がだんだんズレてきて
Well then, try it out.
じゃあ、出してみて
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった